Viewers all over the world, you have seen the downfall of satan.
Glory be to God!
Those under bondage,
those under the dominion of sickness and disease, receive your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Those under dominion,
those under the bondage of sickness, disease, affliction, setback, stagnation, rejection -
receive your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
There are many people in a cage - cage of setback, cage of stagnation, hatred -
receive your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever cage you are in -
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
I release your health, in the name of Jesus!
I release your business, in the name of Jesus!
I release your career, in the name of Jesus!
I release your future, in the name of Jesus!
I release your marriage, in the name of Jesus!
I release your family, in the name of Jesus!
All unclean spirits operating in your life,
all unclean spirits operating in your career,
all unclean spirits operating in your life -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
Unclean spirits operating in your life,
operating in your career,
unclean spirits -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
I can see Jesus' healing touching you.
I can see Jesus' deliverance touching you.
I can see Jesus' blessing touching you.
Right now, begin to fix your life by the authority of Jesus!
Begin to fix your life.
Fix your career!
Fix your business!
Fix your marriage!
Begin to fix your life right now!
Open your lips and begin to fix your life.
Fix your life by the authority of Jesus!
Fix your life!
Fix your career!
Fix your business!
Fix your marriage!
Fix your health!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Open your lips; begin to fix your life!
Fix your business!
Fix your marriage!
Fix your health!
Fix your career!
Begin to fix it!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I can't hear you!
[Amen!]
If God's Words are true for your life, let me hear your 'Amen'.
Let the weak say, "I am strong!"
Let the poor say, "I am blessed!"
Let the sick say, "I am healed!"
In Jesus' name!
[Amen!]
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah!
TT: Mel Flowers 20/04/2019